人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：Iz  奈奈良  红豆包
校对：Iz          总监   IZ
时间轴：今        后期：吉吉
《开心汉堡店》
第三季第二十三集
现在有请休闲棒球联赛替补
And now plan for the recreation league doubles
我的棒球天使  吉恩・贝尔彻
my recreation league angel, Gene Belcher!
我要滑入本垒咯
I'm sliding into home!
你这只是滑步舞吧
I think that's electric slide.
我知道  我不想弄脏我的紧身裤
I know. I didn't want get my capris dirty.
你穿的是棒球运动裤
They're baseball pants.
跟我这件上衣很搭
Well, they go great with this top.
那叫球衣  吉恩
It's also called a jersey, Gene.
不对
No.
大家放松点  别这么较真
Ease up, everybody, back off.
这是他的第一场比赛  太激动人心了
It's his first game. Oh! This is so exciting!
我告诉你什么叫激动人心
I'll show you exciting. Hi-ya!
我还穿了保护蛋蛋的护具
I've got armor for my ding-dong!
用球棒袭击胯下可不是这么个袭击法
Come on. That's not how you hit a crotch with a baseball bat.
你得这样打才行
This is how you hit a crotch with a baseball bat.
伤不了我蛋蛋的东西只会让我变更强
What doesn't break my testicles only makes them stronger!
哇塞  吉恩太彪悍了
Wow, Gene is really athletic.
我爱棒球
I love baseball:
我爱比萨派对  钉鞋
The pizza parties, the spiky shoes,
让球员坐彩车的
the parade at the end of the season
赛季末游行活动
where we ride on a float.
你们看我这样挥手行吗
How's my wave?
你们好  你们好
Hi. Hi.
泰迪  要不要在我们打烊前来杯现煮咖啡
Hey, Teddy, do you want an espresso before we close up?
-一杯什么  -现煮咖啡  怎么样
- A what? - An espresso. Huh?
看看这家伙
Whoa, look at that.
是的  有点小贵
Yeah, it was a little pricey,
但也算是投资了  对吧
but it's an investment, right?
顾客来吃汉堡
Someone comes in for a burger,
他们会说  "鲍勃  你们终于
they'll say, "Oh, Bob, finally
卖现煮咖啡了"
you're selling espresso."
鲍鲍  这就像你上次买的那个电炉
Oh, Bobby, it's like that hot plate you bought.
你当时对那玩意儿也期望很高来着
You had big dreams for that.
它现在在哪儿
Where is it now?
-就在那儿  -好烫
- It's right there. - Oh. Ow, it's hot.
-泰迪  尝尝  免费的  -算了
- Teddy, why don't you try one? It's on the house. - Nah.
尝尝看你喜不喜欢
Well, just to see if you like it.
我不想尝  鲍勃  我在委婉的拒绝你
I don't wanna, Bob. I'm declining politely.
就喝一口  泰迪
Just take one shot, Teddy!
我不喜欢这种小杯子
I don't like those tiny cups!
-就喝一口  -它们显得我的手很大
- Just drink one! - They make it look like I have giant hands!
快点
Come on!
-别逼我  -好吧
- Leave me alone! - Oh, fine.
真的吗  你这么容易就放弃了吗
Really? You're gonna give up that easy?
如果没人喝  也许我可以
Well, if no one's gonna drink this, maybe I'll just...
真难喝
Ugh, that's terrible.
真是  真是
That's... that's...
蒂娜
Hey, Tina.
-你好  泰迪  -你好
- Hi, Teddy. - Hi.
很恶心  是吧
Gross, right?
是的  是一种让人无语的味道
Yeah, it's an acquired taste...
但我已经瞬间适应了
that I just acquired.
击球手  击球手  击球手  击球手
Hey, batter, batter, batter, hey, batter, batter, batter,
hey, batter, batter, batter, batter, batter, batter,
三振出局  你出局了
Strike three! You're out.
我让那娃三振出局了
I made that kid strike out.
是我的功劳  我也是参与者之一
I did that! I'm part of this!
哪个是你的孩子
Which one's yours?
他在那边的休息区给队员们讲笑话呢
Oh, he's down there in the dugout entertaining the troops.
正常的吉恩  邪恶的吉恩
Normal Gene. Evil Gene.
我感觉我能听到头发在长  特别是刘海
I think I can hear my hair growing, especially the bangs.
也许那就是它们被称为刘海的原因
Hey, maybe that's why they call them bangs.
"bang"有"刘海"的意思  同时也可做拟声词"砰"
-小声点  -你喝了几杯咖啡
- Hey, keep it down. - How many espressos have you had?
只喝了一杯  我感觉我这样挺有意思的
Just one. I'm being really interesting right now, I can tell.
通常我的性格是有一点无聊
Usually my personality is a little flat.
你有注意到吗
Did you ever pick up on that?
注意到你有性格吗  没有
That you have a personality? No.
怎么样  教练
How we doing, Coach?
你让所有的孩子都上过场了吗
Have you played all your kids?
是的  应该都上过了
Uh, yeah, I think I got 'em all.
差不多吧  是的  都上过了
Pretty much. Yeah, I got 'em all.
我想是  应该是  对
Yeah, I think, I think so, yeah.
肚皮鼓手呢  我可是让女生都上了
What about Belly Bongo? Come on. I played my girl.
我是男生
I'm a boy.
你得让肚皮鼓手上场  教练
You got to play Belly Bongo, Coach.
好吧  吉恩  你上场
All right, Gene, you're in.
尿尿怎么了
What about urine?
"you're in"[上场]与"urine"[小便]的发音类似
拿上球棒
Grab a bat.
拿上了  现在呢
Done. Now what?
有时我不知道该跟小吉米说什么
Sometimes with Jimmy Jr., I don't know what to say.
但现在我不知道不该说什么
But now I don't know what not to say.
我会一直这么想  "帅哥们
I have all these thoughts, and it's like, "Okay, guys,
谁能第一个亲到我的嘴"
who can get to my mouth first?"
我感觉我挺喜欢染上咖啡瘾的蒂娜的
I think I love Espresso Tina.
多谢  我想小吉米也会喜欢
Thanks. I think Jimmy Jr. will, too.
吉恩要上场了
Oh, Gene's going up to bat! Yay!
加油  吉恩  加油
Go, Gene, go! Whoo!
为什么现在让他上场  这会儿是平局
Why does he have to play now? The game's tied.
吉恩在没压力的情况下都打不出什么好球
Gene doesn't even thrive under no pressure.
好  让球慢慢地滚过来吧  越慢越好
Okay, just roll it at me as slowly as you feel like.
天呐
Oh, God.
一击  二击  三击
Aah! Strike one, strike two, strike three!
我投降
I surrender!
他  好像有点怕啊
He's a, a little tentative out there.
他差点就打到了  对吧
He kind of got a piece of it, right?
-并没有  -好吧  好吧  他没有
- Not really. - No, no, he didn't.
输球不是你的错  亲爱的
It's not your fault you lost, sweetie.
是他的错
It's his fault.
闭嘴  你这第七局的荡...
Hey! Button it, you seventh inning bi...
"seventh inning strech"  美国和加拿大地区棒球的传统  第七局中间有一段休息时间  有时会有歌手唱歌
吉恩  你上场了  是不是很有意思啊
Oh, Gene, oh, you played! Wasn't it fun?
我讨厌棒球  讨厌
I hate baseball! I hate it!
吉恩  等等
Gene, wait!
漂亮的滑垒  宝贝
Oh, nice slide, honey!
没那么糟  吉恩
It's not that bad, Gene.
你犯了几个错误  你三振出局了
You made some errors, you struck out,
有一两个人嘘了你
one or two people booed.
-露易丝  -说句公道话  我还笑了
- Louise. - To be fair, I also laughed.
够了  我以后再以不会
That's it! I'll never set foot
踏进棒球场一步  除非是去裸奔
on a baseball field again except as a streaker!
我放弃了
I quit!
如果你放弃  你就成了半途而废的人
If you quit, you'd be a quitter.
这比输还差劲
That's worse than being a loser.
我觉得可以考虑放弃
Well, let's not dismiss the quitting idea.
-鲍勃  -怎么了
- Bob! - What?
这样也算是捍卫了某种尊严
It has a quiet dignity to it.
某种尊严  你是今天才认识我们吗
Quiet dignity? Have you met us?!
鲍勃  今天的推荐汉堡是什么
Uh, Bob, what's the Burger of the Day?
黑板上什么都没写
I'm looking at an empty chalkboard here.
是用高达奶酪做的一种汉堡
Well, it's something with gouda cheese.
我还在想要给它取个什么名字
I'm still trying to come up with a name for it.
"简直不敢相信高达汉堡"
Woulda Coulda Gouda.
简直不敢相信  这汉堡太好吃了
You Gouda Be Kidding Me. As Gouda As It Gets.
高达高达橡皮糖  几个高达人
Gouda Gouda Gumdrops. A Few Gouda Men.
高达高达两只鞋  有鞋子
Gouda Gouda Two Shoes... comes with shoes.
高达日安  先生
Gouda Day, Sir.
蒂娜  你不许再喝咖啡了
Uh, Tina, no more espresso for you.
小吉米来了
There goes Jimmy Jr.
小吉米  我看到你在骑自行车
Hey, Jimmy Jr., I see you're riding a bicycle.
你知道叫它自行车是因为
Do you know they call it a bicycle
自行车的英文"bycicle"中"bi"有两个的意思
"Bi"有"两个"的意思吗
because "Bi" means two?
说起两个  我们是两个人
Speaking of two, there's two of us.
-要不要去约个会  -好吧
- Do you want to go on a date, by the way? - Uh, okay.
你什么时间合适  明早五点如何
What's good for you? How about tomorrow at 5:00 A.M.?
我知道我能起的来
I know I'll be up.
太好了  说定了  明天见
Great. So it's a date. I'll see you then.
我们一起喝咖啡
We'll get coffee.
糟了  走错路了
Oops, wrong way.
我们要扭转局势
We're gonna turn this sinking ship around.
你只需要一点特别训练
You just need a little extra coaching.
对吗  鲍勃  鲍勃
Right, Bob? Bob?
训练  特别训练
Coaching. A little extra coaching.
-哪方面  -棒球
- In? - Baseball!
-谁来  -你
- From? - You!
是哦  帮吉恩  当然
Oh! Right. For Gene. Sure.
-是的  你  -好  没问题
- Yes, you. - Yeah, okay. Yeah.
我早就该跟你玩接球游戏的
I probably should have been playing catch
那样你现在就会很擅长了
with you for years. Then you'd be good at it.
这里真美啊  老爸  这里是天堂吗
It's so beautiful here. Dad, is this Heaven?
不是天堂  但  但光很美  对吧
It's not Heaven, but the, but the lighting is nice, right?
是一天中最美的时刻
It's a nice time of day.
我看你比赛时
You know, when I saw you playing the game,
我觉得你好像
it looked to me like you were
有一点怕球
a little afraid of the ball.
这些线会让我想到科学怪人
The stitches remind me of Frankenstein!
现在我把球球轻轻抛给你  好吗吉恩
All right, I'm gonna toss it to you easy, Gene, okay?
天越来越黑了  看不太清
It's getting hard to see,
你扔的时候告诉我一声
so let me know when you throw it.
你打到我鼻子了
Oh! You hit me in the nose!
抱歉  我说过我要扔了
I'm sorry! I said I was gonna throw it.
这样  你可以朝我扔一次
Here, you can have a free throw at me.
你不是不会扔球吗
Ow! I thought you couldn't throw!
我瞄准的是你的脚
I was aiming at your feet!
住手  吉恩
Ow! Stop it, Gene!
这次我瞄准的是你的脸
That time I aimed at your face!
那这个怎么样
All right, how about this?
别扔那个
Aah! Don't throw that!
Do not throw that!
看看这个
Hey, look at this.
我搜索了"需要棒球指导的男孩
I Yahoogled "Boy needs baseball help,
失败  无运动细胞
father-son fail unathletic
无可救药的父子  绿松石宝石"
hopeless turquoise jewelry."
绿松石宝石是哪儿来的
Why turquoise jewelry?
因为我一直在找
'Cause I've been looking for some.
又重新流行起来了 总之
It's coming back. Anyway,
看看搜出来什么  "棒球幸运星的
look what came up. "The Deuce of Diamonds' Diamonds
可造之材钻石棒球营"
in the Rough in the Diamond Baseball Camp."
评分有四颗钻呢
It's rated four diamonds!
你好  球手们
Hello there, ballers.
我是棒球幸运星
I'm the Deuce of Diamonds!
我认识他  他是前"胡说八道王子"
Hey, I know him. He used to be the Prince of Persuasia.
啥王子
The Prince of whosia?
教人古代勾引术的老师
A teacher of the ancient art of seduction.
牙普医生有他的视频  我从中学到不少
Dr. Yap had his video. I learned so much.
但现在我有新欢了  有魔力的黑色豆子
But now I have something better, a magic black bean.
-啥  -没什么
- A what? - Nothing.
在追求顶级球手之路上是什么拖了你后腿
What's holding you back from maximum baseball excellence?
猜猜是什么拖了我的后腿
Guess what was standing in my way.
我自己
I was.
真高深
Wow, that's deep.
-相当愚蠢  -闭嘴
- Deeply dumb. - Shh!
我曾经也被三振出局
I was striking myself out.
后来我解放了我身体里那个棒球高手
Then I unlocked the baseball awesomeness inside my body.
看看现在的我
Now look at me.
那不是他打的
He didn't do that.
看看我棒球营的可造之材们
Check out these incredible results
在一天的训练之后
from my one-day Diamonds in the Rough
取得的惊人成绩吧
in the Diamond Baseball Camp.
现在到他挥走厄运的时候了
Now he's Deucing it.
现在大家都挥走厄运了
Now they're all Deucing it.
看啊
Ooh, look at this.
幸运星明天要在城里给棒球营招新
The Deuce is holding his camp in town tomorrow!
只要495美元
And it's only $495.
花495报那个班
$495 for that?
别犯傻了
That's crazy.
这个数  吉恩该直接扔出钱来了
For that kind of money, he should throw in $495.
别这么小气  鲍勃  你爱不爱吉恩
Don't be a cheapskate, Bob. Do you love Gene or not?
-我当然爱了  -恶心
- Of course I love Gene. - Ew!
那就花495块报个班
Then we're spending $495.
哪来那个闲钱
We don't have it!
这种只能在福饼里看见的屁话你也说得出
Oh, go fart in a fortune cookie.
偏心  我要495块报班就说没钱
No fair! I can't have $495,
蒂娜买那么多眼镜就有钱  哼
but Tina can have all the glasses she wants?! Ugh!
我们边喝咖啡边讨论吧
Let's discuss this over a frothy espresso.
我这就做去
I'll go make it.
蒂娜  不许再喝咖啡了
No more espresso, Tina.
我得把她锁屋里
I'm gonna lock her in her room.
不要
No.
也许我可以拿点值钱的东西来卖
Ah, maybe I could sell something valuable.
我在公交上捡了本西语版的《格雷的五十道阴影》
I got a Spanish edition of Fifty Shades of Grey I found on a bus.
是以《暮光之城》男女主人公为原型  由同人作品发展出的成人罗曼史小说  风靡欧美
《格蕾的五十道阴影》[西班牙语]
Cincuenta Sombras de Grey.
别告诉你爸哈
Don't tell your father.
你可以出卖你的灵魂啊
You could sell your soul.
我就卖了  你看看我
I did, and look at me,
我很好
I'm fine.
我有比灵魂价更高的宝贝
I have something more precious than my soul.
当铺
还有这个和这个  永别了
And this one and this one. Good-bye.
-还有这个  -好了
- Ooh, and this one. - Okay.
-别了  我对不起你们  -行了
- Bye-bye. Oh, I'm sorry. - Yeah, okay.
还有这一个  不不不  那个不行
And this one. Oh, no-no-no, not that one. Not that.
我怎么会把它放进来
I don't know how that got in there.
-那啥  -等等  还有这对
- Okay. - Wait, wait. A couple more.
去吧  好啦  这些我要换495块
Bye. Go. Okay. Look, I need $495.
还有那把小手枪
Plus that derringer.
这玩意有点过时了
Look, the kitsch craze is kind of played out.
现在没人喜欢这些娃娃了
No one likes babies.
什么  没人喜欢  不可能
What? Who doesn't? What?
我这收了满满一架子
I got a shelf of 'em.
那个好漂亮  给我看看
Oh! Look at that one! Let me see that one!
老妈
Uh, Mom.
干嘛
What? Oh.
我又天马行空了  抱歉
Going in the wrong direction. I'm sorry.
有精致艺术品
Maybe if you had some fine art
古董钱币  或火枪之类的吗
or antique coins or firearms.
-高级餐馆设备可以吗  -说来听听
- Or high-end restaurant equipment? - Talk to me.
那个怎么样
What about the...?
偷东西去卖  感觉好邪恶
Stealing and pawning. I feel so dirty!
我就说你会爱上干坏事的  老妈
I told you you'd like crime, Mom.
没错  我确实爱
Eh... yeah, I do.
为什么老爸又改变主意要送我
Wounder why dad changes his mind about me going
去棒球幸运星的棒球训练营了
to the Deuce of Diamonds' Baseball Camp?
那是因为他爱你啊
Well, because he loves you.
但你要假装不知道  好吗
But you don't let him know that you know, all right?
你爸他不爱把感情挂在嘴边
He doesn't like to talk about his feelings.
他其实心很软  只是不善表达  懂吗
He's all stunted inside like a big dumb man, all right?
就当是咱俩的小秘密  好吗
It's our little secret, okay?
就像我们周日的美甲足疗之行
Just like our Sunday mani-pedis.
看  他来了
Oh, look, there he is!
你好  幸运星  这是吉恩
Hi, The Deuce. This is Gene.
我虽然有颗棒球运动员的心
I've got the heart of a baseball player
却长了一副当经理的身材
but the body of a manager.
办公室经理
Office manager.
没问题  通通给你解决
No problem, that's what we're here for.
我就是吃棒球这行饭的
Baseball is all I do.
近景魔术揭秘
The Closer of Close-Up Magic.
那不重要
Don't worry about that.
喷墨打印机维修达人
The Iceman of Inkjet Printer Repair?
那些只是...刚好在我车里罢了
Those are just... in my trunk.
那么  关于学费...
Now, about the tuition...
不太好凑  但还是凑齐了
Ah! It wasn't easy, but I got it all.
太好了  现金
Great, cash!
我是说  支票太正式了
I mean, checks are so formal.
这可是不少钱呢
It's a lot of money.
但你确保会有效吧  幸运星
But you guarantee results, right, Deuce?
你最好先在小家伙身上写上你的大名因为
You better write your name on this little guy because
等你来接他时他绝对改头换面到你不认识
you're not gonna recognize him when you pick him up.
我要投个必杀快球  再烫个华丽的发型
I'm gonna have a killer fastball and a magnificent perm.
我去吃个热狗
Whoo! I'm gonna have a hot dog.
这不是吉米・派丝多吗
Hey-hey-hey, Jimmy Pesto!
琳达  谢谢你告我棒球训练营的事
Hi, Linda. Thanks for the heads up about the baseball camp.
很棒吧
Isn't it great?
我对你们最后的期望了  孩子们
Last chance to earn my love, guys.
这笑话我喜欢
I love that joke.
好了  各位  我们开始了
Okay, guys, let's get started.
我先点点这些支票
I'm gonna count these checks,
你们就自己酝酿酝酿热情
and you guys are gonna inject yourself
那也能提升球技的
with some performance-enhancing enthusiasm!
我要转型成运动少年了
I am going to be athletic.
你怎么样  蒂娜
How you doing, Tina?
看起来有点呆啊
You seem a little logy.
呆你妹  你给我闭嘴
Well, you seem a little shut your face.
蒂娜
Tina!
今天是我给她断咖啡的第一天  所以
It's her first day since I cut her off espresso, so...
与狼共舞就是这样子了
Yeah, when you dance with the bear,
停不停全是狼说了算
you can't stop until the bear wants to stop.
咖啡就是那只狼
Espresso's the bear.
别这样  老爸
Come on, Dad.
就让我咬口咖啡豆吧
Just let me bite down on a bean!
不行  咖啡免谈
No! No espresso!
你不能再喝了  你爸也没得卖了
You can't have any and your father can't sell any.
我是说  他做倒是能做
And, uh, I mean, he's allowed to,
但从今往后不会再做给你喝了
he just never, ever will.
行了  话题到此为止
So end of subject.
看看这天气啊
Uh, ooh, look at the sky.
你知道不  我一直就在想
You know what? I've been thinking about it.
也许我该尝一杯  好拓宽我的视野
Maybe I should try it. Broaden my horizons.
不  不行
No, don't!
我看过一篇报导说喝咖啡会导致阳痿
I-I saw a report. It'll shrink your penis.
对  会阳痿的
Yeah, it'll shrink it.
这个报导说会缩  那个报导还说会长呢
One study says it'll shrink, the other says it'll grow.
人得过自己的日子
You got to just live your life.
给我一杯吧  鲍勃
Set me up, Bob.
我的第一笔生意
My first sale.
我们从没想过他能卖出去
We never thought he'd actually sell one.
我要摘下防尘罩了
I just got to take off the dust cover.
摘下防尘罩吧
Take off that dust cover.
哪儿去了
Where is it?!
我的天  它不见了
Oh, my God, it's gone.
真奇怪啊
Oh, how odd.
好了  小伙子们  听好了
Okay, guys, listen up.
手套是你们最好的朋友
Your glove is your best friend.
但你不是它最好的朋友
But you are not its best friend.
你是它的老板  你被它惹毛了
You're its boss and you are pissed off.
现在惩罚你的手套
Now punish your glove.
使劲打  让他再也不敢接不住球
Pound it. Make it afraid to miss a ball ever.
你给我老老实实的接球
You've got to start meeting your performance goals!
态度变了  球技也就大有不同了
When you change your attitude, you change your batitude.
开打吧
So swing away.
幸运星教练  你没拿球啊
Uh, Mr. The Deuce, you don't have a baseball.
如果我们真枪实干来
If we played with a real ball,
这半天就光捡球了
we'd spend half the day running after it.
一切尽在你脑中
It's all in your mind.
二垒安打
That's a double in the gap.
本垒打
Home run.
中外野  上一垒
Broken bat, single.
我需要一名替补跑垒员
I'll need a pinch runner.
你说什么  小鬼
What's that, kid?
我说我要一名替补跑垒员
I said I'm gonna need a pinch runner.
你大点声
Speak up, please.
高飞球  有机会
Long fly ball. This could go.
天呐  打墙上了
Oh, no, caught at the wall.
不
No!
也是你打出来的  你让它打墙上的
By you. You hit it, you caught it.
超炫的实时接球
Amazing over-the-shoulder catch.
我被抢了  被我自己
I was robbed. By me.
咖啡机不会长脚跑了的
An espresso machine doesn't just walk away.
你在哪儿  你这个美丽耀眼的大笨蛋
Where are you, you big, beautiful silver bastard?
谁会偷它呢
Who would do this?
蒂娜
Hi, Tina.
干嘛干嘛干嘛啊
What, what, what?!
我就是想打声招呼
I just... I was saying hi.
因为正好路过  所以...
'Cause I just walked in, so...
你刚说干嘛是要干嘛
what do you mean, what?
我的天  怎么以前就没发现你这么烦人
Oh, my God, I never noticed how annoying you are.
都不知道你在说个屁
I can't even understand what you're saying.
我说话本来就结巴  蒂娜
Oh, I have a speech impediment, Tina.
那赶紧治治吧
Well, fix it.
对了  吉恩呢
Hey, where's Gene?
吉恩  吉恩  吉恩
Ah, Gene, Gene, Gene.
你就会问吉恩
That's all you ever talk about.
怎么不问我啊  你看看我
What about me? Look at me.
吉恩在棒球训练营呢
Gene's at that baseball thing.
我俩弟弟也在那儿
My brothers are there, too.
什么
What?!
对哦
Oh, that's right.
吉恩在...
Uh, Gene's at, uh...
棒球幸运星的钻石棒球营
Deuce of Diamonds' Baseball Camp.
打棒球
Playing baseball.
跨过本垒  脱帽示意
Okay, cross home. Tip your cap.
和下一个上场的击球手撞胸庆祝
Chest bump the guy on deck,
以上就是本垒打的流程
and that's a home run trot.
好了  还有问题没
Okay, any questions so far?
什么事都成
About anything at all.
男生女生啊  生活啊  钱啊
Girls, boys, life, money,
喷墨打印机维修啊
inkjet printer repair.
我能成为一名优秀的棒球选手吗
Um, can I be a good baseball player...
虽然我有哮喘
...with asthma?
鲁迪  我要跟你讲个故事
Rudy, I'm gonna tell you a story.
有一个著名的棒球运动员
A famous baseball player...
名字我一时也记不起了
whose name I can't remember right now...
他患有卢伽雷氏症[霍金也是这种病]
had Lou Gehrig's Disease
但他并没有让疾病阻止他
and he didn't let it slow him down.
好励志
That was inspiring.
我和奥利能成为裁判吗
Um, can Ollie and I be umpires?
当然了
Yes, you can.
-你出局了  -你出局了
- You're out of there! - You're out of there!
幸运星  我能克服对球的恐惧心理吗
The Deuce, will I ever get over being scared of the ball?
吉恩  听我说  这么一个小球
Gene, listen to me. You are so much
你不仅比它大  还比它圆
bigger and rounder than that ball,
它该对你恐惧才是
it should be scared of you.
天呐  是吉恩
Oh, no, it's Gene.
我不会伤害你的  棒球
I won't hurt you, baseball.
没关系的  你的任务就是将我打飞
That's okay. It's your job to hit me over the fence.
我爱死你了  吉恩
I love you so much, Gene. Aw.
等下  接个电话
Hold on, getting a call.
是你欠我1100美元・马诺吉安先生
Ugh, Mr. You Owe Me $1,100 Manoogian.
名和姓都够长的
That is a long first name and a long last name.
你好啊  马诺吉安先生
Hey, Mr. Manoogian.
我也一直想找你来着
Well, I've been trying to reach you, too.
我明白
Uh-huh, I see.
知道了  好
Yes, sir. Okay.
现在我就能缴租  所以你放心吧
Well, I could pay the bill now, so you can go ahead
别把我行李扔马路上
and not put my stuff out on the street.
抱歉  你说多少钱
I'm sorry, it's how much?
小冰柜
Minibar?
通常是高级宾馆房间里的配备  冰柜里有酒水饮料等  价格通常很高
酒店就靠这宰你呢
That's where they get you.
好吧  你就等着吧  我马上就过去
All right, well, you know what? Then I'm coming down there.
带着我的兄弟们
And I'm bringing some of my people.
小鬼们  听好了
Okay, guys, listen up.
有时棒球也需要来一场公路旅行
Um, sometimes in baseball you go on a road trip.
下面我们就练习如何挤进那辆球队面包车
So let's practice piling into the team bus over there.
大家都拿好自己的球棒
Now, everybody grab a bat.
琳达
Linda,
看着我  训练营的费用哪来的
look at me. How did you pay for baseball camp?
我卖了我的陶瓷娃娃
Uh... I, uh, I sold my porcelain babies.
等下  我翻箱倒柜的时候看见了
Wait, I saw those when I was tearing the place apart.
你根本没卖掉
So you didn't sell them!
那些是我的备用娃娃
Those are my backup babies.
对  都是次品  你看它们多丑啊
Yeah, that's the B-team. Look how ugly they are.
你想我来软的还是硬的
You can do this the easy way or the hard way.
-蒂娜  -你以为我是跟你开玩笑的吗
- Tina! - Do you think I'm playing here?
我要我的咖啡机  我的头
I need that espresso machine back... oh, my head.
此处为模仿《猜火车》中的片段  片中男主角因毒瘾发作产生幻觉  在天花板上看到朋友死去的宝宝
嗨  蒂娜
Hi, Tina,
我觉得比起我
I think you're more into espresso
你更爱咖啡
than you are into me.
是事实  我爱浓缩咖啡  咖啡
It's true. I love espresso, coffee,
咖啡茶  然后才是小吉米
caffeinated teas, and then Jimmy Jr.
是这个顺序
In that order.
好吧  是我干的
All right, I did it.
我把咖啡机卖了
I sold the espresso machine.
那可是我们的镇店之宝  蒂娜
That machine was the crown jewel of this restaurant, Linda.
是意大利都灵产的
It was made in Turin, Italy.
那可是制造菲亚特汽车的地方
That's where they make... Fiats!
有什么大不了的  纯粹是浪费钱
Big whoop. It was a waste of money.
我宁愿把钱花在吉恩身上
I'd rather waste money on Gene.
你连它正不正规都不知道
You don't even know if this Deuce is legit.
人家有网站的
He has a Web site.
是啊  网站可不是谁都能做的
Yeah, they don't just give those out.
我们现在就去把钱要回来
We're going down there and we're coming back with our money.
或者带回一个优秀的棒球手
Or a really good baseball player.
我觉得你们俩都不要期望太高
I hope neither of you are getting your hopes up.
-蒂娜  再砸一个  -砸那个
- Tina, break another one. - That one.
不
Oh, no.
沙虱汽车旅馆  价格便宜  内有彩电
好  我们到了  大家都下车
Okay, we're here. Everybody out.
我们老爸常来这儿小憩呢
Hey, this is where our dad goes for his naps.
你好  马诺吉安先生
Hi, Mr. Manoogian!
我去
Oh, crap.
不不不  太晚了
No, no, no, too late!
-听着  别这样  -你太晚了
- Listen. Come on! - You're too late!
-别这样  伙计  -别激动
- Come on, man. - Not cool!
你才激动了  听着
You're not cool! Now, listen.
我没有1100的现金
I don't have the whole $1,100 in cash.
但我可以写支票给你
Oh... But I can sign over some checks.
这上面有国旗
Now, this one has a flag on it,
爱国支票可是不会被退回的哦
and patriotic checks never bounce.
不不不  我不要你那什么狗屁国旗支票
No, no, no, I don't need your stupid flag checks, okay?!
不付租金  我就没收你的DVD
Pay me now, or I'm keeping your DVD player.
那不是DVD
It's not a DVD player,
是能放DVD的蓝光播放器
it's a Blu-ray player that also plays DVDs!
-那不就是DVD吗  -才不是
- Well, then, that makes it a DVD player! - No, it doesn't!
这个锅怎么卖
Hey, how much for this hot pot?
这儿不是旧货市场
This is not a yard sale.
-3美元  -好吧  这儿是旧货市场
- Three dollars. - Okay, it is a yard sale.
他们本来是在这儿的
Well, they were here.
太好了  也就是说
Oh, that's great, so
那个叫什么幸运星的  把孩子们
this guy... The Deuce... just takes off somewhere
-都带走了  -看  他的包还在呢
- with all the kids? - Look, he left that gym bag.
看看  有一张沙虱汽车旅馆的毛巾
See, we've got bath towels from the Sand Flea motel
还有装在小袋里漏了的除臭剂
and some crumbled deodorant in a baggy.
看吧  是贵重物品
See, that's valuable.
他会回来拿的
He's got to come back for that.
天呐  琳  我可不想坐在这儿等他
Oh, my God, Lin, I don't want to sit around waiting for him.
我们去沙虱吧
Let's go to the Sand Flea.
对  路上甚至别停下来买咖啡
Yeah, we shouldn't even stop for coffee.
我们还是停下来买杯咖啡吧
But let's stop for coffee.
这些可不够
Okay, this isn't enough.
还差得远呢
You're still way short.
抱歉我没能脱我的短筒袜
Sorry I couldn't move the tube socks.
好吧  如果你想这样玩的话
Okay, fine! If that's how you want to play it,
我们就要来挥两棒了
we're just gonna take some swings...
目标就是你的冷饮贩卖机
at your soda machine.
上吧  各位
Go to it, guys.
可那不是搞破坏吗
But isn't that vandalism?
巴比・鲁斯还把根汁汽水机砸得稀巴烂呢
Babe Ruth used to beat the crap out of a root beer machine.
美国棒球运动员
-看看他现在成什么了  -好吧
- Now look at him. - Okay.
没错  就像那样
Yeah, there you go.
本垒打
Four-bagger.
大满贯
Grand salami.
不错的界外球哦
That's a good looking foul ball right there.
汽水  你让我变胖  也让我强壮
Soda, you made me fat, but you also made me strong!
清理车  快去
Maid cart, get it.
我一会儿再来吧
I'll come back later.
这些娃可真弱啊  我都没看到什么损坏
These boys are very weak. I see no damage.
他们在摧毁你的尊严
They're damaging your pride.
没觉得
Not very much.
天呐  是吉恩
Oh, my God, there's Gene.
吉恩  你在干嘛
Gene, what are you doing?
打棒球啊  看我打得多好
Playing baseball, and I'm great.
看看他的挥棒  鲍鲍  多优雅的动作
Look at his swing, Bobby. Poetry in motion.
我看是慢动作吧
Yeah, slow motion.
有汽水流出来了  可能是含咖啡因的
Some soda's leaking out. It might have caffeine in it.
蒂娜  别去舔
Tina, don't lick that.
不好意思
Do you folks mind?
我们的训练是不对家长开放的
These practices are closed to parents.
还我们的钱  我们就走
Just give us our money back and we'll go.
退款  不行  绝不可能
Refund, no. That's not gonna happen.
对  绝不可能
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
各位  我全照着幸运星说的做了
Guys, I did everything The Deuce told me to
现在我可是棒球高手了
and now I'm excellent at baseball.
-吉恩  你被骗了  -这位先生
- Gene, this is a scam. - Excuse me,
幸运星长耳朵了  听了会伤感情的
The Deuce has ears and feelings.
-对不起了那  -我原谅你
- Well, I'm sorry. - Well, I forgive you.
-你还得退我们钱  -兄弟  别激动
- But now we want our money. - Whoa, bro, easy.
等吉恩下次参加棒球赛的时候
The next game Gene plays,
你会发现他大有长进的
you'll notice a real diff.
可惜的是到时候我就到亚马逊办棒球营了
Too bad, by then, I'll be setting up my winter camp in Arizona.
到沙漠上挥棒[撒尿  一词多义]
Deucing in the desert. Aw,
那你就看不到吉恩打全垒打了
you're gonna miss Gene hitting all those home runs.
你也看不到树叶变黄了
And you're gonna miss the leaves changing.
他技术没变好  琳
He's not better, Lin.
这根本不是什么棒球营
It's not a real baseball camp.
他变好多了
He is so better.
真希望现在就能比一场
I wish there was a game right now.
让你看看
He'd show you, buddy.
好啊  现在来比一场
You know, what? A game right now.
-说干就干  -好啊  说干就干
- Let's do that. - Yeah, let's do that.
我们还是别操之过急
Well, let's not rush into anything.
我的训练得花一段时间
Some of my training takes a little time...
来吸收
to sink in.
别谦虚了  幸运星
Oh, don't be modest, The Deuce.
你心里有数的
You know what you're doing.
他有天赋  他自己说的
He's gifted; He said so.
他要去TED演讲呢
He's gonna do a TED Talk.
是这样  我得走了
Okay, look, I got to go.
不不不不不  你哪儿都不能去
No, no, no, no, you're not going anywhere.
这里的人刚好够在那边的空停车场
We've got enough people here for a game
打一场比赛
in that vacant lot right there.
如果吉恩安打成功
Now, if Gene gets a hit...
当然他是不会成功的  因为你是骗子
which he won't, because you're a fraud...
钱就归你了
you keep the money.
否则的话  你就要全额退款
If not, we get a full refund.
-听起来好复杂  -我也没听懂
- That sounds really complicated. - I didn't get it either.
-打球  -打球
- Play ball! - Play ball.
*在这自由国家*
*O'er the land of the free*
美国国歌最后两句
*勇士的家乡*
*And the home of the brave.*
一垒是幸运星的除臭剂塑料袋
Okay, first base is The Deuce's baggy of deodorant,
二垒和三垒是他的旱冰鞋
second and third are his Rollerblades,
本垒是他的痔疮垫
and home is his hemorrhoid pillow.
开打
Play ball!
你可以的  吉恩
You can do it, Gene.
来一个安打  让你老爸失望  知道吗
Get a hit and disappoint your father. Okay.
不中  不中  不中  不中
No hit, no hit, no hit, no hit!
加油  吉恩
Come on, Gene.
痔疮垫正上方重重地给它来一击
Wait for a big fat one right over the ass pad.
来了哦  吉恩
Here it comes, Gene.
没什么好怕的
Nothing to be afraid of.
天呐  你打中了
Oh, my God, you hit it...
我是说  我当然知道你打得中
I mean, of course you hit it,
看看是谁教的
I'm a great coach.
吉恩打中了  安打成功了
Gene hit it. That's a hit.
如果有人接到就不算成功
It's n a hit if somebody catches it.
谁快去接
Call it, someone.
-我来接  -我来接
- I got it! - I got it!
-等下  你想接吗  -你想我才想
- Wait, do you want it? - No, not if you want it.
-我可以让你接  -可我感觉你想接啊
- You can have it. - But it sounded like you wanted it.
快点决定
Make up your minds!
我们一起接吧
Let's share it!
别  别  别一起接
No, no, don't share it!
不
No!
现在是安打了
Now it's a hit.
他还在跑呢
Hey, he's still running.
快扔给一垒
Throw to first.
扔给一垒
Throw to first base!
你真是个混蛋  鲍勃
Ah, you're such a dick, Bob.
上面有芥末呢  真的芥末
That had some mustard on it. For real.
-不  -安打成功了
- No! - It's a hit!
这是个错误  它没成功
It's an error, not a hit.
吉恩成功了  混蛋
Gene got a hit, you jerk.
你瞎了吗
You're blind.
-戴副隐形眼镜吧  -我嫁你才是瞎了
- Put some lenses in those things! - I'm blind to marry you!
你干脆把家卖了得了  你这个小偷
Why don't you steal home, you thief?
-东西都给你偷光了  -你喜欢咖啡机
- You've stolen everything else. - You love a coffee machine
-胜过喜欢你儿子  -别用手指我脸
- more than you love your son. - Get your finger out of my face.
-你滚吧  -别用手指我脸
- You're out of here, pal! - Get your finger out of my face!
-我教教你怎么做人  -拿开你的猪蹄
- Stuff it up your crackerjacks! - Your fat finger!
-幸运星走了  -我去
- Hey, there goes The Deuce. - Oh, crap.
不不不不
Oh, no, no, no, no.
我会想他的
I'm really gonna miss that guy.
他把魔法给了我们  自己默默离开了
He gave us his magic and then he disappeared.
就像"湿齿轮青蛙"乐队一样
Just like Toad the Wet Sprocket.
成立于1986年的美国摇滚乐队
我们现在要去披萨派对了吗
Are we going to the pizza party now?
不是
No.
贝尔彻先生  我们明年再战吧
Hey, Mr. Belcher, just wait till next year.
别  别那样  你要干嘛
Don't. Don't do that. What are you doing?
别那样
Don't do that.
看吧  鲍勃  一切都是值得的
See, Bob, it was all worth it.
吉恩重拾了信心
Gene learned confidence.
从一个骗子那儿[一词多义]
From a confidence man.
我信心倍增[很容易骗]  感觉不错
I got conned good. And that ain't bad.
好吧  吉恩高兴  我就高兴了
I guess I'm happy that Gene's happy.
但那咖啡机真的让我很自豪来着
But that espresso machine just really made me proud,
-就是这样  -就那块垃圾吗
- that's all. - That dirty hunk of junk?
没有了才好呢  那对蒂娜不好
I'm glad it's gone. It wasn't good for Tina.
蒂娜呢
Where is Tina?
请于早上十一点前退房
那壶咖啡是一周前的了
That pot is a week old.
我还往里扔了烟头
I put my cigarettes out in that.
你要加奶或加糖吗
Do you want cream or sugar?
*你肉眼看不见*
*You can't see it*
*它是电流*
*It's electric!*
*你得亲自感受*
*You gotta feel it*
*它是电流*
*It's electric!*
*它在摇摆呢*
*Ooh, it's shakin'*
*它是电流*
*It's electric!*
*她像电流一样摇摆*
*She's a-movin' like electric*
*她动作真优美*
*She sure got the boogie*
*你抓不住*
*Now you can't hold it.*
*它是电流*
*It's electric!*